

CJIES TAN

FRONT END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Name:

Xi Jie Tan 陳熙杰

Fmail:

cijies@gmail.com

Phone:

+886-978-109-929

Website:

https://cjies.com

Nationality:

Malaysian

EDUCATION

Computer Science B.Eng

National Cheng Kung University Tainan, Taiwan (2010 - 2014) Major in web development and UI design.

SKILLS

Frontend

Javascript/ES6+ - Proficient CSS/Sass/CSS-in-JS - Proficient React/Flow - Proficient Ionic/angularJS - Intermediate

Backend

node.js - Proficient Django/python - Intermediate Docker - Intermediate Jenkins/Travis CI - Intermediate GraphQL - Basic

Languages

English - Professional Proficiency Mandarin - Native Cantonese - Fluent Japanese - Intermediate (N3)

PROFILE



I am a software engineer with 5+ years experience, mainly skilled in web application development (React, Flow, Webpack, GraphQL, Docker) and mobile web app development (Ionic, Cordova, React and etc).

I am adaptive and welcome challenges, whether it is cross-platform or different-form factor products, or customization requirements from different partners.

EXPERIENCES

Senior Front End Engineer

Appier, Taipei

Jul 2017 - Present

- Leaded frontend team to support both tactical day-to-day business operations and product requirements.
- Rebuilt frontend web app from the ground up, developed and designed related components and modules in monolithic architecture.
- Introduced type systems into producton-ready product progressively.
- Role as Agile Coach, lead the team to hit feature/function deadlines with stable team velocity and strong motivation.

Tech skills: React/Redux, Flow, styled-components, Django, GraphQL, etc

Front End Developer

iCHEF Co. Ltd., Taipei

Mar 2016 - Jun 2017

- Developed a web CMS application for restaurant POS.
- Designed and coded a large in-house component library for react apps.
- Created a cross-platform deploy tool to deliver products easier and faster.
- Participated in many community-organized meetups to sharing experiences and new findings.

Tech skills: React/Redux, Django, Electron, Docker, etc

Front End Engineer

Sep 2014 - Feb 2016

Galaxy Software Services, Taipei

- Positioned as main front-end engineer in design team.
- Architectured a common build scripts for web development.
- Developed a hybrid mobile application which support iOS & Android platform.
- Worked with software developers from different departments to build a large scaled software application.

Tech skills: Ionic, angularJS, Cordova, Kendo, .net MVC